andysbestsites.com 2017-05-15

# Privacy Statement | AndysBestSites

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**  
This policy covers how AndysBestSites.com, and the group of sites belonging to AndysBestSites.com, including but not limited to, AndysPhotoPost.com, MaxBoys.com, CellPhoneBoys.com, KubasPicks.com, and RobbiesBoys.com (and any others added to this group) treats any personal information that AndysBestSites.com might have collected and received, including information related to your past use of any AndysBestSites services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address and that is not otherwise publicly available.

Hereafter, in this document, AndysBestSites refers to all the above mentioned sites in the AndysBestSites group.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the AndysBestSites group does not own or control, or to people that AndysBestSites does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**  
The AndysBestSites group collects personal information if you register with any AndysBestSites group site as a user, when you use any AndysBestSites services, when you visit the AndysBestSites website or the pages of certain AndysBestSites partners.

AndysBestSites automatically receives and records information on our server from your browser, including your IP address and any page(s) or content that you request. This information is anonymous and is not linked to any of your personal details that we might have stored. This type of information is complied and analyzed in aggregate format and is used only for general research and statistical analysis.

AndysBestSites may use your information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and to conduct research.

AndysBestSites will not under any circumstances give out any personally identifiable information that might be stored about you such as email addresses or any other details to anyone! We have a ZERO tolerance policy for SPAM!

**In short**  
AndysBestSites respects your privacy, any information we might have will not be disclosed or given away to anyone else or any third party. AndysBestSites will refuse to disclose ANY information regarding the User unless otherwise required by order of a court of competent jurisdiction, a subpoena properly issued by a court of competent jurisdiction, or upon the advice of our Legal Counsel in cases where we in good faith believe or we become aware that the User has engaged in illegal activity such as credit card fraud or any other serious breaches of our Terms of Service.
